let MCQS = [{
    question: "Which of the following command is used to start a REPL session?",
    choice1: "$ node",
    choice2: " $ node start",
    choice3: "$ node repl",
    choice4: "$ node console",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: " Which of the following module is not a built-in node module?",
    choice1: "zlib",
    choice2: "https",
    choice3: "dgram",
    choice4: "fsread",
    answer: 3
},
            {
            question: "Which of the following method of fs module is used to get file information?",
    choice1: "fs.open(path, flags[, mode], callback)",
    choice2: "fs.stat(path, callback)",
    choice3: "fs.readFile(path, flags[, mode], callback)",
    choice4: "None of the above.",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "Which of the following shortcut command is used to kill a process in Node.js?",
    choice1: "Ctrl + B",
    choice2: "Ctrl + K",
    choice3: "Ctrl + T",
    choice4: "Ctrl + C",
    answer: 3
},
            {
            question: "How many Node object methods are available?",
    choice1: "21",
    choice2: "19",
    choice3: "18",
    choice4: "25",
    answer: 2
},
            {
            question: "Which of the following code print the platform of operating system?",
    choice1: "console.log('platform : ' + os.platform);",
    choice2: "console.log('platform : ' + os.platform());",
    choice3: "console.log('platform : ' + os.getPlatform());",
    choice4: "None of the above",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "What is the default scope in the Node.js application?",
    choice1: "Global",
    choice2: "Local",
    choice3: "Global Function",
    choice4: " Local to object",
    answer: 1
},{
               question: "Which of the following types of applications can be built using Node.js?",
    choice1: "Web Application",
    choice2: "Chat Application",
    choice3: "RESTful Service",
    choice4: "All of the above",
    answer: 3
},
            {
               question: "Which of the following is a GUI-based debugging tool for Node.js?",
    choice1: "Node Inspector",
    choice2: "REPL",
    choice3: "Console",
    choice4: "Core node debugger",
    answer: 0
},
            {
               question: "Which of the following method is used to compare the placement of two nodes in the DOM hierarchy (document)?",
    choice1: "cloneNode()",
    choice2: "compareDocumentPosition()",
    choice3: "getFeature()",
    choice4: " getUserData()",
    answer: 1
}];